博伊德：前情提要。
BOYD: Previously on From...
(音乐盒播放)马丁：森林里一片黑暗。
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING) MARTIN: There's darkness in the forest.
你甚至无法想象的噩梦。
Nightmares you can't even begin to imagine.
(咕哝，喊叫)
(GRUNTING, SHOUTING)
我的血现在就是你的血。
My blood is your blood now.
每次我看到一些非常奇怪的东西，我都会看到这个符号。
Every time I see something really weird, I see this symbol.
(尖叫声)
(SCREAMS)
我见过这个。
I've seen this.
就像在幻觉里还是别的什么？
Like in a vision or something?
塔比莎：不，是在隧道的墙上。
TABITHA: No, on the walls in the tunnels.
维克多说他的母亲想救孩子们
Victor said his mother wanted to rescue the children
被锁在塔里的东西。
that were locked in the tower.
这是让所有人回家的唯一方法。
That it was the only way to get everyone home.
一直以来我都以为孩子们想吓唬我，
All this time I thought the children were trying to scare me,
但如果他们只是寻求我的帮助呢？
but what if they're just asking for my help?
(蝉嗡嗡叫)你听到了吗？
(CICADAS BUZZING) Do you hear that?
帮帮我!
Help me!
请!求求你，我需要帮助！
Please! Please, I need help!
她在睡梦中说话。
She was talking in her sleep.
博伊德：她说什么？
BOYD: What did she say?
“他们触摸，他们打破，他们偷窃。
"They touch, they break, they steal.
这里没有一个人是自由的。
No one here is free."
博伊德：现在这里有别的东西了。一些新的东西。
BOYD: There's something else here now. Something new.
今晚任何人都不能安全入睡。
It's not safe for anyone to go to sleep tonight.
你们每一个人..。带他上楼！
Every one of you... Get him upstairs!
...他妈的要死了！马上把他弄出去！
...is gonna fucking die! Get him outta here now!
埃尔金：我刚刚想起我的梦。
ELGIN: I just remembered my dream.
有一个穿着白色衣服的男孩，
There was this boy all dressed in white,
他不停地重复同一句话。
and he kept repeating the same phrase.
“他们来了……
"Here they come...
(蝉嗡嗡作响)“……他们来找三个人，
(CICADAS BUZZING) "...they come for three,
“除非你停止旋律。”
"unless you stop the melody."
(哽咽)
(CHOKING)
巴克塔：我知道这一点。
BAKTA: I know that one.
这是一首古老的童谣。
It's an old nursery rhyme.
(尖叫)“他们接触，他们打破，
(SCREAMING) "They touch, they break,
“他们偷窃，这里没有一个人是自由的。
"they steal, no one here is free.
“他们来了，他们三个人来了，
"Here they come, they come for three,
“除非你停止旋律。”
"unless you stop the melody."
朱莉！停止播放!(尖叫声)
Julie! Stop! (SCREAMING)
(尖叫声)
(SCREAMING)
(蝉嗡嗡作响)
(CICADAS BUZZING)
他们在楼上。
They're upstairs.
(关门)
(DOOR CLOSING)
你妈妈和..。
Your mom and...
维克多带伊森去了餐厅。
Victor took Ethan to the diner.
嘿，呃，博伊德...
Hey, uh, Boyd...
你应该上楼去，以防他们需要你的帮助。
You should go upstairs just in case they need your help.
(蝉嗡嗡作响)
(CICADAS BUZZING)
那孩子应该选一件舞会礼服，
That kid should be picking out a prom dress,
而不是躺在那里就像..。
not laying in there like...
问题是有太多我们不知道的东西。
The problem is there's too much we don't know.
这就像翻开一本书，从中间开始
It's like opening a book and starting from the middle
或者试着想象拼图是什么样子的
or trying to imagine what a jigsaw puzzle looks like
当你所拥有的只是一些随机的碎片，对吗？
when all you have is a few random pieces, right?
甚至是那些有用的东西，比如角或边。
And not even the helpful ones, like corners or edges.
只是他妈的含糊其辞。
Just vague fucking...
诀窍是你找到了两个相连的部分。
The trick is you find two pieces that connect.
那么至少你有了一个开始的地方。
Then at least you have a place to start.
(蝉嗡嗡作响)
(CICADAS BUZZING)
嘿，嘿。你们打算去哪儿?
Hey, hey. Where are you going?
我们要和莎拉谈谈。
We need to talk to Sara.
(蝉嗡嗡作响)
(CICADAS BUZZING)
(引擎隆隆作响)
(ENGINE RUMBLES)
(刹车发出尖叫声)
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
好吧，如果我们再也睡不着了，那还有什么意义？
Well, if we can't sleep anymore, then what's the point?
我告诉你，我们他妈的都该走了。
I'm telling you, we should all just fucking go.
拿些补给，出发，看看我们能找到什么。
Get some supplies, set out, and see what we can find.
博伊德已经试过了。
Boyd tried that already.
是啊，也许博伊德不是一切的终结，
Yeah, well, maybe Boyd isn't the end-all,
无所不能，无所不能。
be-all answer to everything.
(叹息)
(SIGHS)
我们到底在这里做什么？兰德尔是个混蛋。
What are we even doing out here? Randall was an asshole.
是啊，你也是个混蛋，
Yeah, well, you're an asshole, too,
我不会把你留在这里等着腐烂。
and I wouldn't leave you out here to rot.
啊，我操。
Aw, fuck me.
终于离开我那该死的房间了
Finally get out of my goddamn room
我在执行收集身体的任务。
and I'm on corpse-collecting duty.
去看看下面的情况。
Go check out down there.
埃尔金，这边走。
Elgin, this way.
感谢您的光临。
Appreciate you coming.
做一些有用的事情感觉很好。
It feels good to do something useful.
哦，你做的已经够多了。
Oh, you've done plenty.
你的梦想，
That dream of yours,
就我们所知，这将被证明是这个问题的答案。
for all we know that'll prove to be the answer to this.
听起来很奇怪。
Weird as that fucking sounds.
是啊，也许吧。
Yeah, maybe.
戴尔：你会想看看这个的！
DALE: You're gonna want to see this!
我不认为这家伙已经死了。
I don't think this guy's dead.
哦，见鬼。
Oh, shit.
操。
Fuck.
噢。
Oh.
你不是说这里会有死掉的怪物吗？
Didn't you say there'd be dead monsters out here?
(呼气)
(EXHALES)
银弹到此为止。
So much for silver bullets.
嗯。把他抬上车。
Yeah. Get him in the van.
哦，妈的。
Aw, fuck.
把他抬上车！好吧。
Get him in the van! Okay.
(尖叫声)
(SCREAMS)
上帝啊！
Jesus!
(尖叫声)
(SCREAMS)
她的脉搏很好很强
Her pulse is nice and strong
她深吸了一口气。
and she's taking big, deep breaths.
让我们看看这个。
Let's see here.
(尖叫)塔比莎：哦，我的天。天哪。发生什么事了呢？
(SCREAMS) TABITHA: Oh, my God. Oh, my God. What's happening?
哦，发生什么事了？我不知道!
Oh, what's happening? I don't know!
到底怎么回事？
What's going on?
发生什么事了呢？我不.。我不知道!
What's happening? I don't... I don't know!
想点儿办法吧!想点儿办法吧!(尖叫声)
Do something! Do something! (SCREAMS)
吉姆：哇，哇！
JIM: Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
朱莉！朱莉！
Julie! Julie!
天哪!吉姆：这是什么？
Oh, my God! JIM: What is this?
我不知道。
I don't know.
(尖叫声)
(SCREAMING)
法蒂玛：玛丽埃尔！
FATIMA: Marielle!
(尖叫声)
(SCREAMING)
玛丽埃尔！
Marielle!
嘿，嘿。嘿，看着我。
Hey, hey. Hey, look at me.
玛莉儿，玛莉儿，跟我说话
Marielle, Marielle, talk to me!
(尖叫声)
(SCREAMING)
(QUE SERA，SERA(无论将是什么，都将是)播放)
(QUE SERA, SERA (WHATEVER WILL BE, WILL BE) PLAYS)
♪♪当我还是个小男孩的时候
♪♪ When I was just a little boy
♪♪我问我父亲
♪♪ I asked my father
♪♪“我将会是什么？”
♪♪ "What will I be?"
♪♪“我会很帅吗？”
♪♪ "Will I be handsome?"
♪♪“我会变得富有吗？”
♪♪ "Will I be rich?"
♪♪这是他对我说的话
♪♪ Here's what he said to me
♪♪Que sera sera
♪♪ Que sera sera
♪♪不管是什么都会是
♪♪ Whatever will be will be
♪♪未来不是我们能看到的
♪♪ The future's not ours to see
♪♪Que sera sera
♪♪ Que sera sera
♪♪未来会是什么样子
♪♪ What will be will be
♪♪现在我有了自己的孩子
♪♪ Now I have children of my own
♪♪他们问他们的父亲
♪♪ They ask their father
♪♪“我将会是什么？”
♪♪ "What will I be?"
♪♪“我会漂亮吗？”
♪♪ "Will I be pretty?"
♪♪“我会变得富有吗？”
♪♪ "Will I be rich?"
♪♪我温柔地告诉他们
♪♪ I tell them tenderly
♪♪Que sera sera
♪♪ Que sera sera
♪♪不管是什么都会是
♪♪ Whatever will be will be
♪♪未来不是我们能看到的
♪♪ The future's not ours to see
♪♪Que sera sera
♪♪ Que sera sera
♪♪未来会是什么样子
♪♪ What will be will be
♪♪Que sera sera♪♪
♪♪ Que sera sera ♪♪
(蝉嗡嗡作响)
(CICADAS BUZZING)
莎拉：那么，这应该有什么帮助呢？
SARA: So, how is this supposed to help?
博伊德：当我们在森林里时，
BOYD: When we were in the forest,
你说一个穿白衣服的小男孩叫你上树去。
you said a little boy in white told you to get into the tree.
就是那棵树让我进了那个该死的房间
It's the same tree that put me in the goddamn chamber
这一切都是从那里开始的。
where all this started.
莎拉：所以...
SARA: So...
博伊德：嗯，原来埃尔金做了一个梦，梦到一个穿白衣服的小男孩。
BOYD: Well, it turns out Elgin had a dream about a little boy in white.
给他讲了一段童谣。
Told him part of a nursery rhyme.
保拉在死前一直重复的那句话。
The same one Paula kept repeating before she died.
“他们触摸，他们打破，他们偷窃，
"They touch, they break, they steal,
“这里没有一个人是自由的。
"no one here is free.
“他们来了，他们三个人来了，
"Here they come, they come for three,
“除非你停止旋律。”
"unless you stop the melody."
你觉得这有什么意义吗？
That make any sense to you?
不是的。
No.
关于那个小男孩你还有什么能告诉我的吗？
Anything else you can tell me about the little boy?
他是想帮我们。
He was trying to help us.
好的，所以这个随机的小孩子跑来跑去
Okay, so this random little kid is running around
一个神奇的森林做得好吗？
a magical forest doing good?
突然出现在人们的梦里然后..。
Popping up in people's dreams and...
我不认为他真的是个小男孩。
I don't think he really was a little boy.
赶快。
Come on.
嘿，莎拉，听着。
Hey, Sara, listen up.
现在就是这样。
This is it right now.
当我告诉你你仍然有机会
When I told you there was a chance that you could still
做些好事，这样你就可以帮助这里的人们。
do some good, that you could help the people here...
就在现在，
It's right now,
你懂的?
you understand?
好吧。
Okay.
就在那边。
It's right over there.
(蝉嗡嗡作响)
(CICADAS BUZZING)
好的。就是这个。
All right. This is it.
这整件事就是一个..。有一个..。
This whole, whole thing was a... there was a...
就在这里有人被锁在墙上。
There was someone chained to a wall right here.
就在这里。然后就有了一个洞
Right here. Then there was a hole
它下降了40，50英尺。
that went down 40, 50 feet.
然后我有了..。
And I had...
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我能听到。
I can hear it.
音乐。
The music.
它就在这里。
It's here.
你说什么呢？
What are you talking about?
音乐盒。
The music box.
这是..。它就在这里。
It's... It's here.
哪里?
Where?
就在那里。
Right there.
(呼吸不稳定)
(BREATHING UNSTEADILY)
它就在这里。
It's here.
那里有..。这里没有音乐盒，莎拉。
There's... There's no music box here, Sara.
是的，不，是有的。的确有。
Yeah, no, there is. There is.
我可以.。我能听到，我告诉你，我...我可以.。
I can... I can hear it, I'm telling you, I... I can...
怎么了？
What's wrong?
(呼吸不稳定)
(BREATHING UNSTEADILY)
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我能听到他们的尖叫声。
I can hear them screaming.
什么？
What?
那里有..。那里有..。有一件事。
There's... There's... There's something.
有一件事。
There's something.
它就在这里。
It's here.
这伤害了他们。
It's hurting them.
(尖叫声)
(SCREAMS)
博伊德，他妈的怎么回事？
Boyd, what the fuck is going on?
嘿，莎拉，莎拉。说话..。说话..。跟我说说。
Hey, Sara, Sara. Talk... Talk... Talk to me.
“他们来了，他们三个人来了。”
"Here they come, they come for three."
它需要他们！
It needs them!
它需要他们留下来。它需要他们..。
It needs them to stay. It needs them to...
好吧。(尖叫声)
Okay. (SCREAMS)
好吧。我们得把她弄出去。赶快。
Okay. We gotta get her out of here. Come on.
肯尼，肯尼，快点！嗯。
Kenny, Kenny, come on! Yeah.
快点，伙计。
Come on, come on, come on, buddy.
抬起来。我们走吧。赶快。(尖叫声)
Lift up. There we go. Come on. (SCREAMING)
没事的。没事的。我很抱歉，我很抱歉。
It's all right. It's all right. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
莎拉：不，不要！停止播放!停止播放!
SARA: No, don't! Stop! Stop!
博伊德：好的。好吧。
BOYD: Okay. Okay.
好吧。好吧。
Okay. Okay.
好的。
All right.
它在嘲笑你。
It's laughing at you.
什么？
What?
把它带回镇上。
For bringing it back to town.
让它重获自由。
For setting it free.
它想要伤害我们。
It wants to hurt us.
它想让我们受苦。
It wants to make us suffer.
它变得如此兴奋
It got so excited
当它碰到你的胳膊时。
when it touched your arm.
博伊德：我要怎么阻止这一切？萨拉?
BOYD: How do I stop this? Sara?
(尖叫)我怎么才能阻止它？
(SCREAMS) How do I stop it?
朱莉。朱莉？
Julie. Julie?
朱莉。
Julie.
朱莉？朱莉。
Julie? Julie.
朱..。朱莉。
Ju... Julie.
(尖叫)朱莉。
(SCREAMS) Julie.
朱莉和其他人。嗯。
Julie and the others. Yeah.
他们快要死了。
They're dying.
当他们死后，
And when they die,
那就太晚了。
it'll be too late.
(气喘吁吁)
(PANTING)
你得让它停下来！
You need to make it stop!
好吧。让什么停下来？
Okay. Make what stop?
音乐！音乐！
The music! The music!
你必须让音乐停下来！
You have to make the music stop!
好的，怎么做？
Okay, how?
我怎么才能阻止我看不见的东西？
How do I stop something I can't see?
我不知道!
I don't know!
好的，好的，好的。(尖叫声)
Okay, okay, okay. (SCREAMS)
噢。好的。好的。(尖叫，哭泣)
Oh. All right. All right. (SCREAMING, CRYING)
好吧。
Okay.
蒂莉：深呼吸。
TILLIE: Just breathe.
(水泡)
(WATER BUBBLING)
就这样。
That's it.
深呼吸。
Just breathe.
闭上你的眼睛。
Close your eyes.
让我们祈祷吧。
Let's pray.
是的，尽管我走过
Yea, though I walk through
死亡阴影之谷..。
the valley of the shadow of death...
我将无所畏惧，
I will fear no evil,
因为你与我同在。
for Thou art with me.
你的杖和你的杖安慰我..。
Thy rod and Thy staff they comfort me...
马蒂亚斯？
Matthias?
把枪拿去，锁在棚子里。
Take the guns and lock them in the shed.
我不想让他们在房子里。
I don't want them in the house.
我们设法熬过了那晚。
We managed to make it through the night.
现在我们只需看看今天的情况。
Now we just have to see about today.
好吧。
Okay.
吉姆。
Jim.
赶快。
Come on.
我有件事要做，
There's something I have to do,
我需要你说这没什么。
and I need you to say it's okay.
维克多最后一次见到他母亲时
The last time Victor saw his mother,
她告诉他，有孩子被锁在一座塔里。
she told him that there were children locked in a tower.
如果她帮了他们，
That if she helped them,
然后每个人都可以回家了。
then everyone could go home.
我不明白。
I don't understand.
所有..。我见过的这些孩子，
All... All these children I've been seeing,
我一直梦见一座塔..。
the dreams I've been having about a tower...
如果她是对的呢？
What if she was right?
如果救朱莉的唯一办法就是找到那座塔呢？
What if the only way to save Julie is to find that tower?
猫。
Tabby...
亲爱的我知道我知道这听起来很疯狂。
Honey, I know, I know it sounds crazy.
我对这个地方有一个理论
I had a theory about this place
差点害死我。
that almost got me killed.
好吧，这是不同的。
Well, this is different.
多么?
How?
就是这样。
It just is.
(嘲讽)
(SCOFFS)
吉姆，我们的女儿躺在那个房间里
Jim, our daughter is laying in that room
就像从噩梦中走出来的东西。
like something out of a nightmare.
她昨晚打电话找我，
She called for me last night,
而我却什么也帮不了她。
and I couldn't do anything to help her.
我只是站在那里。
I was just standing there...
我所能想到和看到的就是
And all I could think and see was
托马斯躺在该死的地板上。
Thomas lying on the fucking floor.
我不能。我不能，吉姆。
I can't. I can't, Jim.
我们不能坐在这里做最好的打算。
We can't sit here hoping for the best.
维克多的母亲离开了这个地方
Victor's mother left this place,
然后她就再也没有回来。
and she never came back.
无论她去做什么，她都再也没有回来。
Whatever she went to do, she never came back.
(呼吸不稳定)
(BREATHING UNSTEADILY)
维克多不得不一个人在这里长大。
Victor had to grow up here alone.
如果这种事发生在你身上怎么办？
What if that happens to you?
我知道呀。
I know.
这就是为什么我需要你告诉我我可以走了。
That's why I need you to tell me that it's okay for me to go.
我一定要试一试，吉姆。请。
I have to try this, Jim. Please.
当Julie醒来的时候，她会饿的。
When Julie wakes up, she's gonna be hungry.
我们让她最喜欢吃。
We make her favourite.
嘿。我们把食物带回家。
Hey. We brought home food.
哦，太好了。
Oh, good.
嗯，维克多，我能和你说几句话吗？
Um, Victor, can I talk to you for a minute, please?
维克多有麻烦了吗？
Is Victor in trouble?
不，不。
No, no.
你来帮我。
You come help me.
呃..。
Uh...
你说你母亲想救孩子们
You said your mother wanted to rescue the children
被锁在塔里的东西。
that were locked in the tower.
你知道去塔楼的路吗？
Do you know the way to the tower?
嗯。
Mm.
但是我..。我认识这条路
But I... I know the way
到瓶子树那里。
to the bottle tree.
什么？
The what?
(叹息)
(SIGHS)
(喃喃低语)
(MURMURING)
这就是你去塔楼的路。
This is how you get to the tower.
你.。你一定要去参观瓶子树。
You... You have to visit the bottle tree.
你能带我去那里吗？
Can you take me there?
我也这么想。
I think so.
你能给我们一点时间吗？
Can you give us a second?
吉姆，我得尝尝这个。
Jim, I have to try this.
我至少得试一试。
I have to at least try.
我只是.。
I just...
我知道呀。我知道呀。我知道，宝贝。我知道呀。
I know. I know. I know, baby. I know.
(呼气)
(EXHALES)
(抽泣)
(SOBBING)
那么，我们该怎么办呢？
So, what are we supposed to do?
(蝉嗡嗡作响)
(CICADAS BUZZING)
我们回镇上去。
We head back to town.
等等，什么？
Wait, wait, wait, what?
她刚说音乐盒在这里。
She just said that the music box is here.
它就在这里。我们必须找到它，我们必须..。
It's here. We have to find it, we have to...
是啊，你想让我们怎么做？
Yeah, how do you expect we do that?
我不知道,
I don't know,
但我敢肯定，这不是通过回到镇上！
but I'm pretty sure it's not by going back into town!
这里的人的生命危在旦夕！
People's lives are at stake here!
嘿，我不需要他妈的提醒我什么是危险！
Hey, I don't need a fucking reminder of what's at stake!
我们在这里无能为力。还没。
There's nothing we can do here. Not yet.
听着，我们正在处理的事情超出了我们的范围……
Look, we're dealing with things that are beyond our scope of...
我们现在知道的比今天早上知道的要多。
We know more now than we knew this morning.
这是一场胜利。
That's a win.
好吧。
Okay.
嗯。那么，我们在做什么.
Yeah. So, what are we...
我们该怎么跟人们说？
What are we supposed to tell people?
我们告诉人们，我们正在努力解决这个问题。
We tell people that we are working on it.
我们现在能做的最好的事情就是帮助人们
The best thing we can do now is help people
感觉更平静一点。
feel a little more calmer.
让他们感觉不那么害怕。
Help 'em feel less afraid.
你能做到吗？
Can you do that?
嗯。
Yeah.
好人。
Good man.
(蝉嗡嗡作响)
(CICADAS BUZZING)
(人们在含糊地聊天)
(PEOPLE CHATTING INDISTINCTLY)
嘿。
Hey.
你还好吗？
You all right?
为什么人们总是在答案显而易见的时候问这个问题？
Why do people always ask that when the answer's obvious?
听着，伙计，昨晚的事我很抱歉。
Look, man, I'm sorry about last night.
把你放在那个房间里，我们只是想...
Putting you in that room, we were just trying to...
这是我的错。
It was my fault.
我的狗屎不见了。
I lost my shit.
宝拉是那个在危机中表现出色的人。
Paula was the one who was good in a crisis.
我从未意识到我们是多么脆弱。
I never realised how fragile we are.
我们是多么容易就打破了。
How easily we break.
我在楼下像个白痴一样做饭。
I was downstairs making dinner like an idiot.
你也无能为力。
There was nothing you could've done.
这不是任何人的错。
This was nobody's fault.
嗯。
Yeah.
这不是任何人的错。
Nobody's fault.
嗯。
Yeah.
他怎么样了？
How's he doing?
我只是无法想象如果发生这样的事情我会怎么做。
I just can't imagine what I'd do if something like that...
如果是你的话。(呼气)
If it was you. (EXHALES)
(叹息)
(SIGHS)
嘿，过来。
Hey, come here.
不是我干的。
It wasn't me.
我们结婚吧。
Let's get married.
今天。
Today.
(咯咯笑)是的。
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
听着，我们不知道会发生什么，
Look, we have no idea what's gonna happen,
或者你爸爸会不会想办法...
or if your dad's gonna find a way to...
(咯咯地笑)
(CHUCKLES)
如果这就是结束，那么我希望这一切和你一起结束。
If this is the end, then I want it to end with you.
我想结婚。
I wanna get married.
好吧。
Okay.
好吧?
Okay?
(笑)好的，好的，当然。嗯。
(LAUGHS) Okay, yeah, sure. Yeah.
(敲门)
(KNOCKING)
(玻璃碎了)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(玻璃格格作响)
(GLASS RATTLING)
(倒吸一口气)
(GASPS)
呃..。
Uh...
(玻璃碎了)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(呼气)
(EXHALES)
这就是你在我的酒吧里做的事？
So, this is what you're doing with my bar?
这是一个思维实验。
It's a thought experiment.
阿。
Ah.
我以前觉得这很有帮助
I used to find this helpful
当我发展我的，嗯.
when I was developing my, um...
你死了。
You died.
对，是这样。
Correct.
好吧。
Okay.
好吧，只是想确认一下我们的想法是一致的。
Well, just wanted to make sure we were on the same page.
(呼出重气)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
你不问我是不是真的吗？
Well, aren't you gonna ask me if I'm real?
我想这是某种由压力引起的精神错乱，
I imagine this is some sort of stress-induced psychosis,
你很快就会消失
and you will disappear soon enough
靠你自己。
on your own.
那么这一切到底是要做什么呢？
So what's all this supposed to do?
这是一种重新定位我的视角的方式。
It's a way of reorienting my perspective.
我在试着..。
I'm trying to...
试图找到一种不同的方式来看待这个符号。
Trying to find a different way to look at this symbol.
为什么？
Why?
(叹息)为什么.
(SIGHS) Why...
因为我一直看错了。
Because I've been looking at it wrong.
(呼气)
(EXHALES)
一定有答案的，我只是..。
There's gotta be an answer here, I'm just...
我看不出来。
I'm not seeing it.
(叹息)
(SIGHS)
你知道我只是在想..。
You know I just thought...
什么？那是什么？
What? What is it?
你换了蒸馏器。
You changed the still.
不用谢。
You're welcome.
我觉得你想得太多了。
I think you're overthinking it.
哦，是吗，死去的汤姆？
Oh, do you, dead Tom?
以什么方式？嗯？
In what way? Hmm?
你已经知道你要做什么了。
You already know what you have to do.
塔比莎告诉过你她在隧道里看到了这个符号。
Tabitha told you she saw this symbol down in the tunnels.
问题是，
The question is,
你愿意在多大程度上去寻找答案？
how far are you willing to go to find answers?
下到那些地道里去简直是疯了。
Going down into those tunnels would be insane.
即使它救了朱莉的命？
Even if it saves Julie's life?
哦，操。
Oh, fuck.
你知道吗，我甚至不知道我会不会在下面找到任何东西！
You know, I don't even know if I'd find anything down there!
你当然知道。这是自然的设计。
Of course you do. It's natural design.
同样的原因你的大脑在你的头骨里，
Same reason your brain's in your skull,
你的心脏在肋骨后面。
your heart's behind your ribs.
大自然会永远把最珍贵的东西
Nature will always put what's most precious
在最难到达的地方。
in the spots most difficult to reach.
这地方没有一样东西是天然的。
Nothing about this place is natural.
不对。
Wrong.
这地方一点都不熟悉。
Nothing about this place is familiar.
这是有区别的。
There's a difference.
(呼出重气)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
如果有答案的话..。
If there's answers to be found...
当然，这是一个..。这是一个很大的假设，
And granted, that's a... That's a big if,
他们就会在那里。
that's where they'll be.
好吧，那我该怎么做？
All right, so I'm supposed to what?
我应该听取一些人的建议。
I'm supposed to take advice from some...
你撞上了一座正在倒塌的房子
You ran into a house that was falling down
拯救塔比莎
to save Tabitha
而她甚至都不在那里。
and she wasn't even there.
你知道吗？
And you know what?
如果可以选择，我会再次做同样的事情。
Given the choice, I'd do the same thing again.
那你就是个他妈的白痴。就像.。
Well, then you're a fucking idiot. Like...
(笑)
(LAUGHS)
(两人都笑了)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
你不会在道德上做出选择
You don't make moral choices based
关于你所期望的结果。
on the outcomes you expect.
你根据你是否认为它们是正确的来制作它们。
You make them based on whether or not you think they're right.
当我跑进那所房子的时候，我没有想过
When I ran into that house, I wasn't thinking
关于电车问题，或者决定论，或者...
about the Trolley Problem, or determinism, or...
我根本没想过这些。
Wasn't thinking of any of that.
那边有个16岁的女孩需要你的帮助。
There's a 16-year-old girl over there who needs your help.
你埋葬宝拉了吗？
Did you bury Paula?
什么？
What?
你埋葬宝拉了吗？
Did you bury Paula yet?
上帝啊。
Jesus Christ.
我会去做的。
I'll do it.
我去找几个人来帮忙。
I'll go and find some people to help.
博伊德？
Boyd?
嗯。
Yeah.
你已经尽你所能了。
You're doing the best you can.
(门打开)
(DOOR OPENING)
操他妈的！
Fuck it!
(铃声叮当)
(BELL CLANGING)
(叮当作响)
(CLANGING)
你要把枪收起来吗？
You putting the guns away?
嗯。唐娜担心把它们留在家里。
Yeah. Donna was worried about leaving them in the house.
不，这很聪明。你需要帮忙吗？
No, it's smart. You need a hand?
不，我就快做完了。
No, I'm just about done.
(咕噜声)
(GRUNTS)
(哽咽)
(CHOKING)
没关系的。(嘘)
It's okay. (SHUSHING)
没关系的。没关系的。
It's okay. It's okay.
你只是要比我们其他人走得早一点。
You're just gonna go a little sooner than the rest of us.
一切都是一个系统。
Everything's a system.
一切都是相互关联的。
Everything's connected.
(深呼吸)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
一切都会好起来的。
Everything's gonna be fine.
他妈的我的生活。
Fuck my life.
(倒吸一口气)
(GASPS)
(深呼吸)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
不，不，不！(轻敲手电筒)
No, no, no, no, no, no! (TAPPING FLASHLIGHT)
他妈的狗屎！赶快!
Fucking piece of shit! Come on!
(深呼吸)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(生物尖叫)
(CREATURE SCREAMS)
(呼吸颤抖)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
好吧。
Okay.
好的，我来处理。
Okay, I got this.
很简单。
Easy peasy.
太他妈的容易了。
Easy fucking peasy.
(车门吱吱作响)
(DOOR CREAKS)
上面有人吗？
Anybody up there?
告诉你吧。
Tell you what...
如果你在上面..。
If you are up there...
你真他妈是个混蛋，你知道吗？
You're a real fucking asshole, you know that?
你喜欢这样吗？
You enjoying this?
如果哈特里在这里，哈特里会说，
If Khatri were here, Khatri would say,
“上帝以神秘的方式行动。”
"God moves in mysterious ways."
哦，对，对，因为哈特里有个计划。
Oh, yeah, yeah, 'cause Khatri had a plan.
他认为你把他放在这里是有原因的。他.。
He thought you put him here for a reason. He...
他以为我们会走进那片树林
He thought that we were gonna walk out into those woods
就像布奇·卡西迪和他妈的圣丹斯小子！
like Butch Cassidy and the motherfucking Sundance Kid!
他一直这么想，直到那个时候
He thought that right up until the time
其中一个割断了他该死的喉咙！
one of those things slit his fucking throat!
他最后一口气做了什么？
What did he do with his last breaths?
他祈祷了。
He prayed.
他喘着气说出了那个该死的祈祷
He gasped out that fucking prayer
这样你就会知道。
so that you would know.
这样他就能向你表明他从未失去信心。
So that he could show you that he had never lost faith.
你知道吗，混蛋？
You know what, motherfucker?
我不是来祈祷的。
I ain't here to pray.
如果你不是什么睡前故事的话
If you are anything other than some bedtime fucking story
我们告诉自己，然后你会告诉我为什么！
that we tell ourselves, then you will tell me why!
为什么你让我觉得我可以解决这件事？
Why you made me think I could fix this?
某个他妈的英雄会把这些人带回家
Some kind of fucking hero gonna lead these people home,
当我只是个傻逼的时候
when all I am is a dumb motherfucker
一直让人丧命的人！
who keeps getting people killed!
该死的!
Damn it!
你他妈的。你觉得这很好笑？
You fuck. You think this is funny?
哈?你在上面的什么地方他妈的笑了？
Huh? You up there somewhere having a fucking laugh?
哈?哈?
Huh? Huh?
只是..。回答我！
Just... answer me!
回答我！
Answer me!
哈?
Huh?
你说点什么吧!
Say something!
你知道的..。
You know...
篡改邮箱是联邦犯罪。
Tampering with a mailbox is a federal crime.
(敲门)
(KNOCKING)
进来。
Come in.
她怎么样了？
How's she doing?
她的情况越来越糟。
She's getting worse.
她，嗯，她变冷了。
She's, um, she's getting cold.
真的是这样吗？
Is this really it?
事情就这样结束了吗？
Is this how it ends?
(叹息)我不知道。
(SIGHS) I don't know.
你知道，自从她走下公交车
You know, ever since she walked off that bus
我实际上允许我自己
I actually allowed myself
相信这一切都是有计划的。
to believe that there was a plan to all of this.
我们在这里注定要做的事。
That there was something we were meant to do here.
但没有...
But there's no...
没有什么宏伟的设计。
There's no grand design.
我们都会死在这里。
We're all gonna die here.
而这一切都将是徒劳的。
And all this would have been for nothing.
你知道吗，我爸爸曾经说过，
You know, my dad used to say,
“我很难看到这件毛衣
"It's hard to see the sweater
“当你只是一根线时。”
"when you're only just a thread."
直到现在我才真正明白他的意思。
I didn't really know what he meant 'til now.
所有被困在这里的人。
All of the people that have gotten stuck here...
也许我们不是可以回家的人，
Maybe we aren't the ones that get to go home,
但也许我们在这里所做的
but maybe what we did here
让下一个来的人更容易。
makes it easier for the people who come next.
也许我们就是他们回家的原因。
Maybe we're the reason that they get to go home.
仅仅因为我们只是一根线
Just because we're only a thread
并不意味着我们不重要。
doesn't mean we don't matter.
这就对了。
There ya go.
你最不需要的就是哈特里缠着你
Last thing you need is Khatri haunting you
凌驾于一切之上。
over everything else.
现在已经太晚了。
It's too late for that.
朱莉和玛丽埃尔。
Julie and Marielle.
兰德尔。
Randall.
莎拉说他们快死了。
Sara says they're dying.
一旦他们走了，
And once they're gone,
不能把精灵放回瓶子里。
there's no putting the genie back in the bottle.
不管这是什么，它都在等着我们
Whatever this thing is, it just waits for us
去睡觉然后..。
to go to sleep and then...
就像保拉一样。
Like Paula.
嗯。
Yeah.
她说音乐盒在那里，
She said the music box is there,
就在那片空地上。
right there in the clearing.
只是它不在那里。
Only it's not there.
就像看一本说明书
Like looking at an instruction manual
缺了太多页。
with too many pages missing.
我怎么会..。我怎么能..。
How am I... How am I supposed...
我昨晚见到了我的妻子。
I saw my wife last night.
她看起来怎么样？
How'd she look?
一定要有规则的，唐娜。
There's gotta be rules, Donna.
一定有什么东西我可以拿在手里。
There's gotta be something I can hold in my hands.
一定会有如此..。
There's got to be so...
这是我干的。
I did this.
我把这玩意儿带回来了。
I brought this thing back here.
是的。你当然是这么做的。
Yup. You sure did.
你也给了一大群人更多的时间
You also gave a whole bunch of people a lot more time
如果不是你的话他们会得到更多。
than they would've had if wasn't for you.
你给了我更多时间。
You gave me more time.
你儿子就要结婚了。
Your son is about to get married.
我想，没什么正式的。
Nothing official, I guess.
我们不再有牧师了。
It's not like we have a priest anymore.
他们充分利用了他们所拥有的任何时间。
They're making the most of whatever time they have.
你也应该这么做。
You should do the same.
跟我回殖民地之家吧。
Come back to Colony House with me.
我不会放弃的。
I'm not giving up.
(咯咯笑)我说放弃了吗？
(CHUCKLES) Did I say give up?
(呻吟)
(GROANS)
博伊德，这可能是我们最后几个小时了。
Boyd, this may be the last few hours any of us get.
所以，你为什么不停止做一个该死的殉道者
So, why don't you just stop being a goddamn martyr
来看看你儿子的婚礼吧。
and come and watch your son get married.
当仪式结束时，世界末日还会在这里。
The end of the world'll still be here when the ceremony's done.
(呼气)
(EXHALES)
(门打开)
(DOOR OPENING)
(关门)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(深呼吸)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
孩子：安库伊。
CHILD: Anghkooey.
(倒吸一口气)
(GASPS)
安库伊。安库伊。
Anghkooey. Anghkooey.
孩子们：(低声吟唱)安库伊。
CHILDREN: (WHISPERING, CHANTING) Anghkooey.
安库伊。安库伊。
Anghkooey. Anghkooey.
安库伊。安库伊。安库伊。安库伊。安库伊。
Anghkooey. Anghkooey. Anghkooey. Anghkooey. Anghkooey.
安库伊。安库伊。安库伊。安库伊。安库伊。安库伊。
Anghkooey. Anghkooey. Anghkooey. Anghkooey. Anghkooey. Anghkooey.
孩子们：(吟唱)安库伊。安库伊。
CHILDREN: (CHANTING) Anghkooey. Anghkooey.
安库伊。安库伊。安库伊。安库伊。安库伊。
Anghkooey. Anghkooey. Anghkooey. Anghkooey. Anghkooey.
安库伊。安库伊。安库伊。安库伊。
Anghkooey. Anghkooey. Anghkooey. Anghkooey.
安库伊！安库伊！安库伊！安库伊！安库伊！
Anghkooey! Anghkooey! Anghkooey! Anghkooey! Anghkooey!
安库伊！
Anghkooey!
(蝉嗡嗡作响)
(CICADAS BUZZING)
关于孩子们，你母亲还说了什么吗？
Did your mother say anything else about the children?
她怎么能救他们呢？
How was she gonna save them?
我不知道。她所说的就是
I don't know. All she said was that
他们需要她。
they needed her.
这是..。这应该是正确的..。就在这里。
It's... It should be right... right here.
不，不。这些……这些树不是..。
No, no, no, no. These... These trees weren't...
嘿，嘿，嘿。那是很久以前的事了，维克多。
Hey, hey, hey. It was a long time ago, Victor.
也许.。也许我们拐错弯了。
Maybe... Maybe we took the wrong turn.
(玻璃叮当声)
(GLASS CLINKING)
完毕..。在这里。
Over... Over here.
(蝉嗡嗡作响，玻璃叮当作响)
(CICADAS BUZZING, GLASS CLINKING)
谁把瓶子放在那里的？
Who put the bottles there?
我不知道。
I don't know.
这就是我发现她的地方。
This is where I found her.
你妈妈？
Your mom?
是的，在所有人都死后，我来找她。
Yeah, after everyone died, I came looking for her.
她的身体..。
Her body was...
她没能爬到树上。
She didn't make it into the tree.
你说撞到树上是什么意思？
What do you mean into the tree?
噢。
Oh.
来。
Come.
这是一棵很远的树。
It's a faraway tree.
怪物进入殖民地之家的那晚，
The night the monsters got into Colony House,
朱莉说你们都是爬到树上逃出来的。
Julie said you both escaped by climbing into a tree.
他们总是带你去不同的地方，
They always take you different places,
你永远不知道你会在哪里结束，
and you never know where you'll end up,
但我妈妈说这一次很特别。
but my mother said this one was special.
它会把她带到塔上，
That it would take her to the tower,
敬孩子们。
to the children.
然后呢？
And then what?
呃..。
Uh...
我只记得这些。
That's all I remember.
噢。嗯。这里。
Oh. Yeah. Here.
我..。
I...
我在里面放了些零食给你。
I put some snacks inside for you.
这里。
Here.
谢谢你，维克多。
Thank you, Victor.
嗯。
Yeah.
穿过去疼吗？
Does it hurt to go through?
不，这就像走进一扇门。
No, it's just like walking through a door.
好吧。嗯。
Okay. Mm.
好吧。谢谢。
Okay. Thank you.
现在回镇上去。
Now go back to town.
注意。
Be careful.
嗯。
Yeah.
(蝉嗡嗡作响)
(CICADAS BUZZING)
(瓶子叮当作响)
(BOTTLES CLINKING)
天哪。
Oh, my God.
我们这是在干嘛？
What are we doing?
他想让它成为一个惊喜。
He wanted it to be a surprise.
他想要的是什么惊喜？
He wanted what to be a surprise?
你总是说这个景色甚至让这个地方
You're always saying that this view makes even this place
看起来像个梦，所以我想。
look like a dream, so I figured.
这样行吗？
Is this okay?
这真是太完美了。
This is perfect.
嘿，我们为什么不直接去找他呢？
Hey, why don't we just go get him?
他有很多心事，你知道吗？
He's got a lot on his mind, you know?
史蒂文斯警长！
Sheriff Stevens!
你做到了。
You made it.
什么，你在开玩笑吗？
What, are you kidding me?
野马挡不住我。
Wild horses couldn't stop me.
(咯咯笑)好的。
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
让我们开始这场演出吧。
Let's get this show on the road.
好的，等等。嗯.。
Okay, wait. Um...
我知道这不算什么过道，
I know it's not much of an aisle,
但你愿意给我这个荣幸吗？
but would you do me the honour?
好了，准备好了吗？嗯。
All right, you ready? Yeah.
你也不用再叫我史蒂文斯警长了。
And you don't have to call me Sheriff Stevens anymore.
好吧。
Okay.
要不我们?
Shall we?
(颤抖地呼出一口气)
(EXHALES SHAKILY)
(呼气)
(EXHALES)
女士优先。
Ladies first.
好吧。嗯.。
Okay. Um...
我父亲有一句话。
My father had a saying.
实际上，他说了很多话，但是...
Well, he had a lot of sayings, actually, but...
(大家都在笑)
(ALL LAUGHING)
嗯，我最喜欢的是……
Um, my favourite one was always...
“生命是一次穿越未知的旅程，
"Life is a journey through the unknown,
“尽管你的眼睛和思想有时可能
"and though your eyes and mind may sometimes
“欺骗你，你的心永远不会说谎。”
"deceive you, your heart will never lie."
从我遇见你的那一刻起，我的心就一直属于你。
My heart's belonged to you since the moment I met you.
你是我一生的挚爱，
You're the love of my life,
只要生命能持续下去。
for as long as that life may last.
所以，你愿意，埃利斯·史蒂文斯，
So, will you, Ellis Stevens,
我有幸成为我的丈夫吗？
do me the honour of being my husband?
这就做。
I will.
(呼气)
(EXHALES)
我给你做了点东西。
I made you something.
(呼气)
(EXHALES)
(呼气)轮到你了。
(EXHALES) Your turn.
(笑)
(LAUGHING)
哦，这是一个很难跟上的表演。
Oh, it's a tough act to follow.
(笑)嗯.
(LAUGHS) Um...
我和家人看到那棵树的那天，
The day my family and I saw that tree,
我们的生活永远改变了。
our lives changed forever.
但我看到你下车的那一天，
But the day that I saw you get out of that car,
那是我生命真正开始的那一天。
that's the day that my life really began.
在这里有太多次我觉得...
There have been so many times here where I felt...
就像我在黑暗中跌跌撞撞。
like I was stumbling in the dark.
但每一次，
But each and every time,
你是指引我走过的那道光。
you were the light that guided me through.
你是我的爱。
You are my love.
你就是我的家。
You are my home.
在黑暗的地方，你是我的光。
You are my light in dark places.
所以..。(清嗓子)
So... (CLEARS THROAT)
你会，
Will you,
法蒂玛·哈桑·罗斯塔米。
Fatima Hassan-Rostami...
你愿意赏光做我的妻子吗？
Will you do me the honour of being my wife?
这就做。
I will.
规则说我们现在接吻。
Well, the rules say we kiss now.
(两人都在笑，都在哭)
(BOTH LAUGHING, CRYING)
唐娜：博伊德？
DONNA: Boyd?
你去哪里了？
Where'd you go?
埃利斯：爸爸，你还好吗？
ELLIS: Are you okay, Dad?
黑暗中的光明。
Light in dark places.
我得走了。
I gotta go.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
嘿。没关系的。
Hey. It's okay.
好吧。
Okay.
噢。天哪。
Oh. Gosh.
我好爱你们。
I love you guys.
好的?
All right?
我也爱你。
Love you, too.
(呼气)
(EXHALES)
我们还能再见到托马斯吗？
Will we get to see Thomas again?
什么？
What?
如果我们死了。
If we die.
我们还能再见到托马斯吗？
Will we get to see Thomas again?
嗯。
Yeah.
好的，我们会的。
Yeah, we will.
爷爷也是吗？
Grandpa, too?
爷爷也是。
Grandpa, too.
也许那时情况就不会那么糟糕了。
Maybe it won't be so bad then.
她喜欢睡在两个枕头上。
She likes to sleep with two pillows.
(斯塔默斯)让我来帮你。
(STAMMERS) Let me help you.
(机架式猎枪)
(RACKING SHOTGUN)
嘿，雷吉？
Hey, Reggie?
这是你干的。
You did this.
一切都很好，直到你进了森林。
Everything was fine until you went into the forest.
嘿。你就是这一切发生的原因！
Hey. You're the reason all this is happening!
好的，嘿，嘿。听着，听我说！
Okay, hey, hey. Listen, listen to me!
听我说。
Listen to me.
我知道你不明白，我知道，
I know you don't understand this, I know,
但我认为这支火炬，就在这里，
but I think this torch, right here,
我想这会帮我解决这个问题。
I think this is gonna help me fix this.
(开枪)(喊叫)
(FIRES GUN) (CRIES OUT)
对不起，博伊德。(机架式猎枪)
I'm sorry, Boyd. (RACKING SHOTGUN)
我一直都很喜欢你。
I always liked you.
(鸣枪)(喊声)
(FIRES GUN) (SHOUTS)
神!
God!
(咕哝着)
(GRUNTING)
哦，他妈的！
Oh, fucking!
(气喘吁吁)
(PANTING)
操!
Fuck!
(蝉嗡嗡作响)
(CICADAS BUZZING)
(咕哝着)
(GRUNTING)
操。
Fuck.
(咕哝着)
(GRUNTING)
他妈的..。操。
Motherfuck... Fuck.
操。操。
Fuck. Fuck.
(咕噜声)(打火机的电影)
(GRUNTS) (LIGHTER FLICKS)
赶快。
Come on.
(播放音乐盒)
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING)
什么？
What?
(播放音乐盒)
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING)
(传来哀鸣的声音)
(VOICES MOANING)
朱莉！嘿。朱莉！
Julie! Hey. Julie!
嘿，朱莉。嘿，朱莉。
Hey, Julie. Hey, Julie.
你听得见吗？
Can you hear me?
你能..。
Can you...
我会把你弄出去的。
I'm gonna get you out of here.
I'll get you outta here.
我现在就把你弄出去。
I'm gonna get you outta here right now.
我们要离开这里。(音乐框点击并播放)
We're getting outta here. (MUSIC BOX CLICKS AND PLAYS)
(音乐盒播放)(呼吸不稳定)
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING) (BREATHING UNSTEADILY)
博伊德！
Boyd!
请。摧毁那个盒子不会结束他们的痛苦。
Please. Destroying that box isn't gonna end their suffering.
你只会延长它。
You'll only prolong it.
不是的。我..。
No. I...
镇上的人会受苦的，
People in this town will suffer,
以你甚至无法想象的方式。
in ways you can't even imagine.
他们都会尖叫着死去。
They're all gonna die, screaming.
(兰德尔、玛丽和朱莉尖叫)
(RANDALL, MARI, AND JULIE SCREAMING)
(尖叫声)
(SCREAMING)
她怎么了？
What's wrong with her?
嘿!没关系的。
Hey! It's okay.
伊森：怎么了？
ETHAN: What's wrong?
她怎么了？
What's wrong with her?
蜂蜜!亲爱的，别这样，别这样。
Honey! Honey, please, please.
(尖叫声)
(SCREAMING)
你认为你需要成为英雄。
You think you need to be the hero.
你认为你需要负责任，去拯救他们。
You think you need to be responsible, to save them.
你再也不用忍受痛苦了。
You don't have to suffer anymore.
你不必害怕。
You don't have to be afraid.
没关系的。所有这些都无关紧要。
It's okay. None of this matters.
我们可以在一起。
We can be together.
(猛地呼出一口气)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
我非常想念你。
I miss you so much.
(倒吸一口气)
(GASPS)
等等，所以，听着，停下来。
Wait, so, look, stop.
所以，不管这是什么东西，
So, so whatever this thing is,
它只是让你来这里聊聊天？
it just lets you come in here for a little chat?
它知道你不会听的。它想让你去战斗。
It knows you won't listen. It wants you to fight.
它希望你有希望，你真的能赢！
It wants you to have hope that you could actually win!
为什么？
Why?
因为希望是让你愿意忍受痛苦的东西。
'Cause hope is what makes you willing to suffer.
希望就是那天把你送进树林的原因。
Hope is what sent you out into the woods that day.
希望让你在我最需要你的时候离我而去。
Hope is what made you leave me alone when I needed you most.
不是你的恐惧滋养了森林，博伊德。
It's not your fear that feeds the forest, Boyd.
这是希望。
It's hope.
(朱莉、兰德尔和玛丽尖叫)
(JULIE, RANDALL, AND MARI SCREAMING)
(播放音乐盒)
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING)
算了吧，博伊德。
Let it go, Boyd.
如果他们今天不死，他们明天就会死。
If they don't die today, they'll just die tomorrow.
(音乐盒播放)(囚犯尖叫)
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING) (PRISONERS SCREAMING)
不是的。
No.
(玛丽、兰德尔和朱莉尖叫)
(MARI, RANDALL, AND JULIE SCREAMING)
(喊声)
(SHOUTS)
(喘息，咳嗽)
(GASPS, COUGHS)
朱莉！
Julie!
哦，你没事的。嘿。
Oh, you're okay. Hey.
(咳嗽)
(COUGHING)
玛丽埃尔，嘿。
Marielle, hey.
嗨!
Hi!
到底怎么回事？
What's going on?
(呼吸不稳)哦，亲爱的。
(BREATHING UNSTEADILY) Oh, honey.
她很好。
She's okay.
朱莉：哦，天哪。你妹妹很好。
JULIE: Oh, my God. Your sister's okay.
嗨，宝贝。没关系的。
Hi, baby. It's okay.
没关系，是的。
It's okay, yes.
(抽泣)
(SOBBING)
(呼吸不稳定)
(BREATHING UNSTEADILY)
去你妈的，混蛋。
Fuck you, motherfucker.
(咕哝着)
(GRUNTING)
你不能打垮我。
You don't break me.
你听到了吗？
You hear that?
你他妈的不能毁了我！
You don't fucking break me!
(叫声)
(BARKING)
把这个喝了。
Drink this.
我很好。
I'm fine.
我知道你是。
I know you are.
就当是为了我。
Do it for me.
没有更多的嗡嗡声了。
There's no more buzzing.
这是不是意味着一切都结束了？
Does that mean it's over?
我当然希望如此。
I sure hope so.
爸爸?
Dad?
妈妈在哪里？
Where's Mom?
孩子：(低声说)安库伊。
CHILD: (WHISPERS) Anghkooey.
你好?
Hello?
孩子：(低声说)安库伊。
CHILD: (WHISPERS) Anghkooey.
(齿轮叮当作响)
(GEARS CLINKING)
孩子：安库伊。
CHILD: Anghkooey.
安库伊。
Anghkooey.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
我真的是
I really am.
这是唯一的办法。
This is the only way.
(尖叫声)
(SCREAMS)
(嘟嘟声)
(BEEPING)
(嘟嘟声加快)
(BEEPING QUICKENS)
噢。
Oh.
请稍等。
Just a moment.
(倒吸一口气)
(GASPS)
(嘟嘟声)
(BEEPING)
现在.。
Ow.
(监视器蜂鸣声迅速提醒)
(MONITOR BUZZES ALERT RAPIDLY)
女人：你感觉怎么样？
WOMAN: How are you feeling?
我在哪儿呢？
Where am I?
圣安东尼医院。我是布罗迪医生。
St. Anthony's Hospital. I'm Dr. Brody.
三天前，一对徒步旅行者在树林里发现了你。
Three days ago a pair of hikers found you in the woods.
你当时昏迷不醒地躺在一条小路边。
You were lying unconscious on the side of a trail.
不是的。
No.
你还记得你在外面做什么吗？
Do you remember what you were doing out there?
不是的。
No.
不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no.
(倒吸一口气)
(GASPS)
(闭幕主题音乐播放)
(CLOSING THEME MUSIC PLAYING)